Josephine Butler 134
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - World Dialogue on Disarmament and Dtente, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - USSR, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1982-1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Baptist General Connection of Virginia, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Afro Readers Unemployment and Undocumented Workers, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Resolutions of the District of Columbia City Council, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Friendship Society 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Friendship Society 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary Tours, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Friendship Society, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Friendship Society, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood Party Meeting Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)